Bank
officials provided safety kit to the Chief Minister.
50,000 hang masks, 50,000 second
layer masks, 240 portal sanitizers, a sanitizer
set and an infrared thermal scanner were handed over to Chief Minister Hemant Soren today at the Chief Minister's residence by ICICI Bank. The
Chief Minister praised the work being done by the promoted Sankat Bank.
He
said that the government is taking necessary steps to prevent, protect and treat the infection.
In this, full support is being received from
various organizations including socio-economic, educational and business.
With the cooperation of the people of the state, we will
definitely be
successful in defeating Corona. On this occasion, ICICI
Bank informed the Chief Minister
that during their 'History in Ours' campaign,
this target will be implemented in all the districts of the state.
Thermal scanners and other promotional
material are being continuously distributed. The
students informed the Chief Minister that the cost of making the
Thalassemia Award at Ranchi Sadar Hospital has been
borne by the bank.
Report by Santosh, associate from Prachi for New Zealand: A
Candy Crush FICCI Like About You
Scientific Study  Material girl from the
best in India is selection rate in
GTB tune plus elections every year baby has become
prosperous want to cry back join the
CNN from the best countries
contact with Chinese has become want to become a
doctor John BMC customer his and gets
purified a
that subscribe to New Zealand channel on YouTube
and press the bell button to see the news first
that contact to inform about the news in news channels
and whatsapp the video
our contact number is
[music]